http://www.addispenser.com/privacy/

Our core business is
designing, developing, and integrating Internet applications and
associated technologies. This ad server software is a fruit of years of knowledge and experience.
This ad server software is 100% pure Java.
Privacy Statement of Yasna Inc.
Information about our Organisation and Web site
Yasna Inc. is a
compnay dedicated to designing, developing, and integrating Internet applications and associated technologies. Our principal activity is software development.
We are based in Canada.
Our privacy policy covers
Yasna Inc.
and Ad Dispenser Website:
Organisation Name:
Yasna Inc.
Address:
81 Cummer Ave.
City, Zip:
North York
,
M2M-2E6
Province:
Ontario
Country:
Canada
Controller:
Yasna Inc.
Web Sites:
http://www.addispenser.com
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.
The services and links of our Web site
Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others.
When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.
Our Web site does not include links to third party Web service providers.
Automatic Collection of Information
We automatically log personal data by
means such as programming or we link information
automatically logged by such
means with personal data about specific individuals.
We do so for the following purposes:
Technical administration of the Web site
Research and development
Marketing
We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals.
Data Collection and Purpose Specification
We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services.
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations.
To access the table of personal data collected and purposes
for which they are used, please
click here
We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below.
If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose:
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.
We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by:
making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorised the collection
of the child's personal data
We do provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on
our home page and wherever we knowingly collect personnal data from children on our Web site.
Disclosure and Visitor Choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations.
Where we disclose your personal data for purposes which are different from those indicated in the
table mentioned above, we offer you the opportunity to consent to disclosure:
Confidentiality / Security
We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method
to send us their personal data.
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that
we have under our control from:
unauthorised access
improper use or disclosure
unauthorised modification
unlawful destruction or accidental loss
All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the
processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of
our visitors' personal data.
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities
except if required by law or other regulation.
Access to the personal data we may hold about you
You can ask us, by:
sending an email (
privacy@addispenser.com
)
whether we are keeping personal data about you.
Upon request, which you can indicate by:
sending an email (
privacy@addispenser.com
)
We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you,
within a week.
- although we may before require proof of your identity -.
We will provide the information
at a charge of
$15
.
We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:
erased
We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data,
but will give reasons for our refusal.
We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.
Privacy Compliance
Our privacy policy is compliant with the following instrument:
OECD Privacy Guidelines
There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation.
We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the privacy
instrument.
Privacy Support
We do not provide our visitors with a contact point for privacy concerns or enquiries.
We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed.
TABLE of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used
other (describe)
other (describe)
other (describe)
other (describe)
Police/Justice data such as civil/criminal actions brought by or against the visitor
other (describe)
